eyetricks.com 2015-12-30

# Privacy Statement

| 

|   
---|---  

**Privacy Statement for eyetricks.com**

BWH Ventures, LLC has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: **eyetricks.com**.

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. 

This site contains links to other sites. **eyetricks.com** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. Certain links on this website are provided by Adtegrity.com, a third party. Please follow this link <http://www.adtegrity.com/privacy.asp> to view Adtegrity.com's Privacy Statement.

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit networkadvertising.org.

We offer a newsletter to our visitors which is used to distribute information regarding our Web Site. We use contact data from our newsletter to send the user information about our company. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below.

From time to time, we run online surveys. Our online surveys ask visitors for contact information (like their email address). We use contact data from our surveys to send the user information about our company. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below.

From time to time, we run contests on our site in which we ask visitors for contact information (like their email address). We use contact data from our contests to send users information about our company. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below.

## Public Forums

This site may make chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

## Choice/Opt-Out

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor.

This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service. 

  1. You can send email to [webmaster@eyetricks.com](mailto:webmaster@eyetricks.com)

## Correct/Update

This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided. 

  1. email [webmaster@eyetricks.com](mailto:webmaster@eyetricks.com)

## Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact:
